Hi, my name is Karanveer. Recently, I've completed my **Google** Certification in User experience. In addition - I've over 5 years of working experience as a front-end developer and web-designer. I have taken a big decision to change my job-role last year, and now I'm learning more about Ui and Ux.

CAREER EXPERIENCE

## Web Designer / Front end developer

Jan 2012 - Dec 2018

Netpyx - Mohali

- **✓** Creating Mobile adaptive screens for iPad, iPhone, etc.
- ✓ Creating Wire frames and High fidelity designs.
- ✓ PSD to html using standard Xhtml / Css3 / Scss practices.
- ✓ Senior instructor for Web design interns at Netpyx.
- Coordinating with Developers and Project Manager.

# Web Designer - Internship

Aug 2011 - Dec 2011

Optimum Technologies - Mohali

EDUCATION

# B-Tech in Computer Science and Engg.

2007 - 2011

Institute of Engineering & Technology - IET Bhaddal

## Google UX Design Professional Certificate

2022

Coursera

- **✓** Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design
- ✓ Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate
- **✔** Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes
- ✔ Create High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes in Figma

### **REACH ME AT**

karanveer75singh@gmail.com

+91 8557956466

### **PORTFOLIO**

Please click here

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Figma Advanced

Html, Css, Scss Old-timer

Visual Studio Code Good

Logic Pro X Advanced

Mac OS

#### LANGUAGES

English Advanced

Punjabi Native

Hindi Nice

French A1

" A UI without Ux is like a dish that looks good but has an awful taste "

karanveer singh